Fire Truck with a Phobia!
Haha!
Did we keep you waiting?
An all new Milky Way special!
We call it... The Flame Tower!
The Flame Tower...?
Shall we begin?
Mhm.
Surprise!
Wow! This looks amazing!
You see? Everyone loves a little bit of a performance.
You really are the best, Dad!
Huh? Is there a fire?
I think it's getting closer...
Fire! Please evacuate!
Fire extinguished!
Ugh...
Aah!!
Urgh! What kind of surprise was that?!
Ah, no, Anna, it's not-
Save it!
No, Anna, wait!
Anna, please don't go!!
Anna...
Jun.
Jun. That fire truck just now was a Metal Cardbot.
That's not important right now. Dang it!
Jun!
What are you doing?
Seems like similar cases have been popping up everywhere these days.
People were having a barbeque in their yard when they were sprayed with extinguisher fluid...
The torch at an olympic relay was put out...
Even candles on a birthday cake were blown out by a fire truck!
Ugh, what is going on in this city...?!
Was it all because of that fire truck?
Probably...
Urgh! I'm gonna find him and make him kneel before Anna and apologize!
You can seal them, but you mustn't reveal the Metal Cardbots.
I know, but...
Ugh! How do I set things straight with Anna, then?
Phoenix Fire.
Huh? Do you know them, Mega Ambler?
Yes. We were part of the same rescue team.
He used to be the bravest firefighter,
always jumping head first into the flames.
He received the Metal Medal, an honor awarded to only the best rescue workers on planet Machina.
If he's such a hero, why's he playing all these pranks now?
I don't think these are pranks. He seems to be genuinely afraid of fire.
Afraid of fire? A rescue worker with a Metal Medal?
I can't be certain. Not without giving him a proper counseling session.
That cowardly fire truck... what do you think he's up to now?
Jun, that's a smoke bomb! Don't touch it, it's not safe.
Oh! Okay...
Hmm...
Confirming Metal Cardbot ID on the planet directly ahead.
Initiating landing.
Error in the controls!
Oh no!
This is bad... the controls aren't working!
Agh!
I had that dream again...
Fire... is just too dangerous.
There must be oxygen for something to catch fire.
For example, when you place a lit candle inside a jar...
Really? Set a trap?
Well, since Phoenix Fire can't stand fire,
let's just make one to lure him out.
Yeah, but a fire will bring real fire trucks as well.
Right. That's a problem...
Hey, you two! Pay attention!
We're sorry!
So, shall we begin the experiment?
Huh?
Is that another fire truck?
It's him!
Where's the fire?
Oh my... Woah... A real fire truck... That's so cool! (FX-italic)
Theo.
Huh? Are you serious?
You're the only one that can help me with this!
Uh, okay... I'll do it!
I'm wondering if there has been a mistake. There's no fire here-
Fire alert! This is a fire alert!
All students, please evacuate immediately!
Huh? Oh no!
There has been a fire! All students, please!
You have to evacuate the building!
It's the real deal?
Let's get out of here!
Stay calm, everyone! Please walk, don't run!
It's okay, everyone! Don't panic! Stay calm!
Jun, where are you going?
I'll go check if there are others who haven't evacuated.
Anna, please take care of our classmates.
Alright. Be careful!
Is that the fire?
There's a fire! Evacuate!
Hehe! Sorry, but it's not a real fire!
What? You tricked me!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Blue Cop, setup!
That's enough, Phoenix Fire!
What's wrong with putting out fires?!
Fire is proof of civilization to the people of this planet.
You shouldn't put out just any fire.
That doesn't concern me!
You don't know how scary fire can be!
All fires need to be put out!
Blue Cop, use your Burst Shot!
Got it!
Burst Shot!
Huh? F-Fire...?
Augh!
That's...
That's Phoenix Fire's Metal Medal!
Fire! Everything will go up in flames if I don't do something!
It's covered in soot. I guess we know how he got a phobia of fire.
Looks like it's time for the doctor to step in.
Mega Ambler, setup!
It's too early to take a break.
Pick yourself up and get back to it!
That did the trick... thanks, Mega Ambler.
So, you're a real doctor after all.
Now, Blue Cop will be able to help Phoenix Fire.
Wake up, Phoenix Fire.
You used to be a brave rescue worker!
What do you know?!
Blue Cop, watch out!
Let's end it with this! Megabolt... Punch!
Megabolt...
Punch!
Now!
Metal Cardbot, Change Up!
Phoenix Fire, sealed!
Haha!
Phew...
I changed out your temperature sensor because it was burnt out.
It might take some time to get used to the new sensor, since it was made here on Earth.
Glad you're okay now, Phoenix Fire!
I'm sorry for causing trouble. Let's be a good team from now on!
The hero has returned.
Glad to have you back.
Hello?
So you were here!
Anna...?! What brings you here?
I thought I'd thank you for what you did.
Here, it's a piping hot apple pie!
Wait, you mean you made this yourself?!
Eat it while it's hot! I think it should still be...
Hot...pie...
I have to put it out!
- Calm down.
- There's no fire...
Ahhh, this is amazing! it's Anna's homemade apple pie!
Hey Uncle Edo, can you bring us some drinks?!
Get them yourself!